We want to talk about HDFC Bank. HDFC
Bank's results have come as per the
estimates, it was quite elevated. This is
my personal view that in front of an elevated
expectation, they had set higher
expectations, so in some certain areas
of the market, one can say that everything did
not explode, but you see
how is the performance on G base and
secondly, the stock is already on the fifth and is
in a strong position, so how will it
react today, what should be done and not only this,
its result and the impact of the reaction will be
on ICC Bank, its result is also
this week only. Sher Khan is joining us
for talking to us in this big,
thank you very much Rahul for talking to us today.
Rahul Malani is joining us.
Rahul, first of all tell us
what is the matter of Gypsy Bank, some people are saying that it has remained
strong, so they have been made Mitter, so
what is the problem, so
first of all, good morning sir,
overall if you see the result, there was a marginal miss in
expectations, but in terms of when you
talk about return ratios, it  So let's
talk about it, HDFC Bank has still
reported around 2% in terms of return on assets in ascending terms,
so the
overall result as per our estimate, in
line paper, overall consensus wise, there is a
slight mistake because the opening was zero
because if you
look at branch expansion, you have seen employee addition
and their return
expected lines are
strong, then the numbers will not be damaged,
Axis Bank and overall HDFC Bank will
post good results but as you have
seen that in Effect 23 there was
HDFC Bank and one Federal Bank,
their deposit mobilization is
higher, so retail deposit mobilization will be an
important factor for this bank
because their loan deposit ratio is
entertaining higher, so they should increase
retail deposits to sustain loan growth to 1920%.